Inventory of the Iris Chang papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Sound recordings
  - Iris Chang interview, WORT radio, Madison, Wisconsin, 1998 November 2 (Box-folder 323: 4)
  - Iris Chang interview, All Things Considered, National Public Radio, 1997 December 3 (Box-folder 323: 5)
  - Iris Chang interview, KEST radio, San Francisco, California, undated (Box-folder 323: 6)
  - Iris Chang interview, WODS radio, Boston, Massachusetts, 1998 November 1 (Box-folder 323: 7)
  - Iris Chang interview, KVI radio, Seattle, Washington, 1998 February 4 (Box-folder 323: 8)
  - Iris Chang interview, These Days, 1998 January 12 (Box-folder 323: 9)
  - Iris Chang interview, unidentified radio station, 1997 January 9 (Box-folder 323: 10)
  - Iris Chang interview, David Brudnoy show, undated (Box-folder 323: 11)
  - Iris Chang interview, WLEA radio, Hornell, New York, undated (Box-folder 323: 12)
  - Iris Chang interview, CKNW radio, Vancouver, Canada, 1997 December 9 (Box-folder 323: 13)
  - Iris Chang interview, The Progressive, 1998 November 2 (Box-folder 323: 14)
  - Iris Chang interview, Oregon Public Broadcasting, undated (Box-folder 324: 1)
  - Iris Chang interview, Forum, KQED radio, San Francisco, California, 1997 December 4 (Box-folder 324: 2)
  - Iris Chang interview, KBOO radio, Portland, Oregon, 1998 February 2 (Box-folder 324: 3)
  - Iris Chang interview, WJHU radio, Baltimore, Maryland, 1997 November 18 (Box-folder 324: 4)
  - Iris Chang interview, 1998 January 24 (Box-folder 324: 5)
- Videorecordings
  - "Authors, Poets, and Storytellers," with Iris Chang as guest, undated; One VHS videotape cassette (Box-folder 324: 6)
    Use copy available on-site for immediate use. Use copy reference number: 2004c22_v_0010676.
    Gary Smolik interviews Iris Chang about her book The Rape of Nanking on "Authors, Poets, and Storytellers."
  - "Japan News Magazine," Japan America Television, 1998 October 3 (Box-folder 324: 7)
  - "The Bookcase with Chris Connelly,", 1998 October 26; One VHS videotape cassette (Box-folder 324: 8)
    Use copy available on-site for immediate use. Use copy reference number: 2004c22_v_0010674.
    Chris Connelly interviews Iris Chang about the paperback release of The Rape of Nanking.
  - Footage relating to Robert Wilson and George Fitch, undated (Box-folder 325: 1)
    Access DVD copy available for immediate viewing. Use Reference ID 2004c22_001_r2015.
  - "Nanking (Fitch/Condon),", undated (Box-folder 325: 2-3)
  - "Demo 2003," Hybride Company (Box-folder 325: 4-5)
    One VHS videocassette and one DVD
  - Promotional film, Rising Sun Pictures, 2003 (Box-folder 325: 6)
  - "Magee's Testament,", undated; One VHS videocassette (Box-folder 326: 1)
    Use copy available on-site for immediate use. Use copy reference number: 2004c22_v_0012596_r01.
    Documentary about David Magee, the son of missionaries, who grew up in Nanking in the 1920s and 1930s, and whose father witnessed the Rape of Nanking, and documented it in letters and amateur filmmaking.
  - "Magee's Testament" and "Denial (Nanjing - 1937) A Work in Progress", undated; One VHS videocassette (Box-folder 326: 2)
    Use copy available on-site for immediate use. Use copy reference number: 2004c22_v_0012596_r02.
    Chinese dubbed over version of a documentary about David Magee, the son of missionaries, who grew up in Nanking in the 1920s and 1930s, and whose father witnessed the Rape of Nanking, and documented it in letters and amateur filmmaking. Included on the recording is a documentary short about how the Rape of Nanking is known in Japan, which includes interviews with soldiers who were participants.
  - "The China Call,", undated (Box-folder 326: 3)
  - Archival footage relating to the Japanese occupation of China (in Chinese), undated (Box-folder 326: 4)
  - Iris Chang interview, Connie Martinson Talks Books, 1996 April 4 (Box-folder 326: 5-6)
  - "The Genocide Factor," episode three, 2001 (Box-folder 326: 7)
- Sound recordings
  - Rape of Nanking conference, 1994 December 10 (Box-folder 326: 8-11)
    Four compact sound cassettes
  - "In the Name of the Emperor,", undated (Box-folder 326: 12)
  - Music by Tom Mulaney, undated (Box-folder 327: 1)
- Videorecordings
  - "Rape of Nanking (Chinese version),", undated (Box-folder 327: 2)
  - "Tea Time--Iris Chang and Michael Honda,", 2000 June 20 (Box-folder 327: 3)
    Access DVD copy available for immediate viewing. Use Reference ID 2004c22_005_r2015.
  - Iris Chang interview, Writer's Block, 1998 March 15 (Box-folder 327: 4)
    Access DVD copy available for immediate viewing. Use Reference ID 2004c22_004_r2015.
  - "The Genocide Factor," episodes one and four, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 327: 5-6)
  - "We Served with Pride,", undated (Box-folder 327: 7)
  - Iris Chang, Nightline, 2001 August 15 (Box-folder 327: 8-9)
  - "A Decade Inside Asian America: A. Magazine Looks Back,", 1999 October 22 (Box-folder 327: 10)
  - "The Rape of Nanking," History Undercover, undated (Box-folder 328: 1)
  - Program on Chinese Americans, Public Broadcasting System, 1999 August (Box-folder 328: 2)
  - Committee of 100's 10th anniversary conference, role model panel, undated; One VHS videotape cassette (Box-folder 328: 3)
    Use copy available on-site for immediate use. Use copy reference number: 2004c22_v_0010677.
    Panel on Asian-American contributions to contemporary American society, featuring Iris Chang.
  - Memorial service for 60th anniversary of Nanking Massacre, 1997 December 13; One VHS videocassette (Box-folder 328: 4)
    Use copy available on-site for immediate use. Use copy reference number: 2004c22_v_0012600.
    Amateur video footage of a memorial event in San Francisco for victims of the Rape of Nanking and the Attack on Pearl Harbor.
  - Aspire conference, undated; One VHS videotape cassette (Box-folder 328: 5)
    Use copy available on-site for immediate use. Use copy reference number: 2004c22_v_0010678.
    Iris Chang delivering the keynote address at the 1999 Aspire conference.
  - "John Rabe," This Week in History, 2000 December 18 (Box-folder 328: 6)
  - "UNA Forum: Combating Racism,", 2001 October 10 (Box-folder 328: 7)
  - NBC Hardball with Chris Matthews, [?] July 2; One VHS videotape cassette (Box-folder 328: 8)
    Use copy available on-site for immediate use. Use copy reference number: 2004c22_v_0010679.
    Chris Matthews interviews Iris Chang about her book The Rape of Nanking and controversy it is generating.
  - "The Chinese Americans," program including an interview with Iris Chang, WLIV-TV, Plainview, New York (Box-folder 328: 9)
  - "The Genocide Factor," episode 2, 2001 (Box-folder 329: 1)
  - Booknotes: Iris Chang, 1997 November 17; One VHS videotape cassette (Box-folder 329: 2)
    Use copy available on-site for immediate use. Use copy reference number: 2004c22_v_0010689.
    Iris Chang being interviewed on the C-SPAN program Booknotes.
  - "Liu Xiuying, Escaper of Nanjing Massacre,", 1997 October (Box-folder 329: 3)
  - Iris Chang appearance, Toronto, Canada, 1997 December (Box-folder 329: 4)
  - Good Morning America Sunday, 1997 December 7; One VHS videotape cassette (Box-folder 329: 5)
    Use copy available on-site for immediate use. Use copy reference copy number: 2004c22_v_0010690.
    Willow Bay and Bill Ritter interview Iris Chang on the ABC Network's Good Morning America, Sunday edition.
  - The Charlie Rose Show, 1998 May 19; VHS videotape cassette (Box-folder 329: 6)
    Use copy available on-site for immediate use. Use copy reference number: 2004c22_v_0010688.
    Charlie Rose interviews Iris Chang on his show.
  - "The Forgotten Holocaust,", 1998 July 5 (Box-folder 329: 7-8)
  - University Laboratory High School 1998 graduation, One VHS videotape cassette (Box-folder 329: 9)
    Use copy available on-site for immediate use. Use copy reference number: 2004c22_v_0010691.
    The 1998 graduation ceremony at University Laboratory High School in Urbana, Illinois, at the Krannert Center for the Performing Arts, featuring Iris Chang as a speaker.
  - "Saturday Appointment,", undated (Box-folder 329: 10)
  - Broadcast on Nanking Massacre, Newsworld, Canadian Broadcasting Corporation, 1997 December 15 (Box-folder 330: 1)
  - "Unit 731--Nightmare in Manchuria,", 1999 February 19 (Box-folder 330: 2)
  - 'The Rape of Nanking According to Winnie," recording of a play by Marge Waterstreet, 1999 May 23 (Box-folder 330: 3)
  - "The Rape of Nanking," videorecording by Nancy James, undated (Box-folder 330: 4)
  - News program featuring Iris Chang, KNTV, San Jose, California, 1998 April 28 (Box-folder 330: 5)
    Access DVD copy available for immediate viewing. Use Reference ID 2004c22_007_r2015.
  - Iris Chang talk and interview, Washington, D. C., 1998 January-March (Box-folder 330: 6)
    Access DVD copy available for immediate viewing. Use Reference ID 2004c22_008_r2015.
  - Iris Chang interview, undated (Box-folder 330: 7)
  - Iris Chang appearance and book signing, War Crimes of the East Symposium, University of Illinois, Urbana-Champaign, 1998 October 10 (Box-folder 330: 8)
  - Documentary on Nanking Massacre (in Chinese), undated (Box-folder 330: 9)
- Open (Boxes 331-349)
- Printed matter in Chinese, 1952-2000 (Box-folder 350: 1-9)
- Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 351: 1)
- Conferences file, 1999-2001
  - Sixth Chinese-American Conference, San Diego, 1999 July 9-11
    - Speech by Iris Chang, 1999 July 10 (Box-folder 351: 2)
    - Other papers, registration form, and publicity materials, 1999 July 9-11 (Box-folder 351: 3)
  - 50 Years of Denial: Japan and Its Wartime Responsibilities Conference, 2001 September 6-9
    - Speeches by Iris Chang, 2001 September 6-9 (Box-folder 351: 4)
    - Program, 2001 September 6-9 (Box-folder 351: 5)
    - Publicity materials, 2001 September 6-9 (Box-folder 351: 6)
- Statement by Iris Chang for press conference, San Francisco, 2001 August 28 (Box-folder 351: 7)
- Photographs depicting Iris Chang, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 351: 8)
- Postcards and booklet relating to Nanking Massacre, 1998 (Box-folder 351: 9)
- Correspondence, 1992-2003 (Box-folder 352: 1)
- Photographs depicting Iris Chang
  - 1992 (Box-folder 352: 2)
  - 1995 (Box-folder 352: 3-4)
  - 1996 (Box-folder 352: 5)
  - 1997 (Box-folder 352: 6-9)
  - 1998 (Box-folder 352: 10-16)
  - 2001 (Box-folder 352: 17)
  - 2003 (Box-folder 352: 18-21)
- Speeches and writings by Iris Chang, 1997-2003
  - The Rape of Nanking: The Forgotten Holocaust of World War II, 1997
    - Draft, 1997 (Box-folder 353: 1)
    - Draft with editors' comments, 1997 (Box-folder 352: 2)
  - The Chinese in America, 2003
    - Outline, 2003 (Box-folder 353: 3)
    - Proofs, 2003 (Box-folder 353: 4)
- Videorecording (VHS) of interview by Iris Chang with Mr. Wei, Nanking Massacre survivor, 1997 (Box-folder 354: 1)
  Access DVD copy available for immediate viewing. Use Reference ID 2004c22_006_r2015.
- Printed matter, 1995-2004
  - Clippings relating to interior design, 2004 (Box-folder 354: 2)
  - Monographs relating to screenwriting, 2000 (Box-folder 354: 3-4)
  - Serial issues relating to Nanking Massacre and Japanese invasion of China, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 354: 5-6)
- Photographs depicting survivors of Bataan Death March, 2003 (Box-folder 354: 7)
- Cameron House materials, 2004
  Related Materials
  Historical photographs of activities and individuals related to the Cameron House are available at the website of that organization, https://cameronhouse.org.
  - Letter and notecards, 2004 (Box-folder 354: 8)
- Printed matter, 1970-2004
  - Monographs, 1970-1998
    - Studies on Asian-Americans and the Chinese population in Vietnam, 1982-1998 (Box-folder 355: 1-2)
    - Writings by Anna Chennault, 1970-1988 (Box-folder 355: 3-4)
  - Serial issues, 2000-2004
    - General, 2004 (Box-folder 355: 5)
    - Chinese Holocaust, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 355: 6)
- Lists of books and movies, 2004 (Box-folder 355: 7)
- Materials relating to memorial services for Iris Chang, 2004
  - Register of funeral attendees, 2004 (Box-folder 356: 1)
  - Cards from floral tributes, 2004 (Box-folder 356: 2)
  - CD-ROM containing images of Iris Chang, 2004 (Box-folder 356: 3)
- Speeches and writings by Iris Chang, 1970-1989
  - Research materials used for The Chinese in America, 1970-1989 (Box-folder 356: 4-8)
  - The Rape of Nanking: The Forgotten Holocaust of World War II, 1996-1997
    - Outline, notes, and fragments, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 357: 1-22)
    - Drafts, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 357: 23-26)
    - Drafts, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 358: 1-8)
    - Drafts, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 359: 1-2)
    - Notes, 1996 (Box-folder 359: 3-6)
- Writing by Barbara Masin, 2004 (Box-folder 359: 7)
- Articles about Iris Chang, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 359: 8)
- Awards and memorabilia, 1986-2004
  - Wood blocks used for making prints, 1986 (Box-folder 360: 1-3)
  - Award plaque, Max Beberman Distinguished Alumni Award, 1997 June 6 (Box-folder 360: 4)
  - Award plaque, New Association of Chinese Americans, New York City, 1998 June 28 (Box-folder 360: 5)
  - Diploma cover for honorary doctorate, California State University at Hayward, 2004 (Box-folder 360: 6)
  - United States Achievement Academy 1984 National Awards book (Box-folder 360: 7)
- Notecard files, 1988-2004
  - Welfare reform and job creation in the United States, 1988 (Box-folder 361: 1)
  - Wedding guests, 1991 (Box-folder 361: 2-3)
  - Ideas for writing projects and speeches, 2004 (Box-folder 361: 4)
- Academic career file, 1981-1990
  - University High School, Urbana, Illinois, notebook for Chinese language class, 1981 (Box-folder 362: 1)
  - University of Illinois, Urbana-Champaign, 1987-1990
    - Student papers, 1990 (Box-folder 362: 2)
    - Assignments and readings, 1990 (Box-folder 362: 3)
    - Notes on lectures and course readings, 1990 (Box-folder 362: 3-10)
    - Notes on lectures and course readings, 1990 (Box-folder 363: 1-4)
    - Open Wide, literary magazine edited by Iris Chang, 1987-1988
      - Editorial file, 1987 (Box-folder 363: 4)
      - Submitted writings, 1987 (Box-folder 363: 6-7)
      - Proofs and photographs, 1987 (Box-folder 363: 8)
      - Printed copies, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 364: 1-2)
- Chicago Tribune file, 1988-1989
  - Correspondence and conference materials, 1989 (Box-folder 364: 3)
  - Articles written by Iris Chang, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 364: 4-5)
- Mensa Bulletin, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 364: 6-16)
- Correspondence, 1998-2004
  - General, 1998-2004
    - 1998 (Box-folder 365: 1-2)
    - 1999 (Box-folder 365: 3)
    - 2002 (Box-folder 365: 4)
    - 2003 (Box-folder 365: 5-6)
    - 2004 (Box-folder 365: 7)
  - Committee of 100, 2004 (Box-folder 365: 8)
  - MacArthur Fellows Program, 1999 (Box-folder 365: 9)
  - National Writers Union, 1999 (Box-folder 365: 10)
  - Speaking engagements, 1998-2004
    - 1998 (Box-folder 365: 11-12)
    - 1999-2004 (Box-folder 365: 13)
- Notes by Iris Chang, 1999 (Box-folder 365: 14)
- Subject file
  - Personal health and pregnancy issues
    - Brochures, flyers, and pamphlets, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 366: 1-4)
    - Catalogs, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 366: 5-7)
    - Directories, 2001 (Box-folder 366: 8-9)
    - Monographs, 1988-1999 (Box-folder 367: 1-2)
    - Newsletters, 1992-2002
      - 1992-1996 (Box-folder 367: 3)
      - 1997-2000 (Box-folder 367: 4)
      - 2000 (Box-folder 367: 5)
      - 2001 (Box-folder 367: 6)
      - 2001-2002 (Box-folder 367: 7)
    - Articles and reports, 1987-2001
      - 1987-1989 (Box-folder 367: 8)
      - 1992-1994 (Box-folder 368: 1)
      - 1995-1997 (Box-folder 368: 2)
      - 1998-1999 (Box-folder 368: 3)
      - 2000 (Box-folder 368: 4-7)
      - 2001 (Box-folder 368: 8)
      - 2001 (Box-folder 369: 1-8)
  - Universities and colleges, 1994-1998
    - Application forms, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 370: 1-3)
    - Brochures and catalogs, 1996-1998
      - 1994 (Box-folder 370: 4)
      - 1995 (Box-folder 370: 5-8)
      - 1996 (Box-folder 370: 9)
      - 1996 (Box-folder 371: 1-8)
      - 1998 (Box-folder 371: 9)
- Brett Douglas file, 1995-2006
  - Correspondence, 1995-2006
    - 1995 (Box-folder 372: 1)
    - 1995-1996 (Box-folder 372: 2)
    - 2005-2006 (Box-folder 372: 3)
  - Personal essays, 1995 (Box-folder 372: 4-5)
  - Curriculum vitae, 1995 (Box-folder 372: 6)
  - Miscellany, 1995 (Box-folder 372: 7)
- Correspondence and enclosures, 1990-2004
  - Chang, Shau-Jin and Ying-Ying, 1998 (Box-folder 372: 8)
  - Clinton, Bill, 1999 (Box-folder 372: 9)
  - Job search, 1990-1997
    - 1990-1992 (Box-folder 372: 10)
    - 1994 (Box-folder 372: 11)
    - 1994 (Box-folder 373: 1-2)
    - 1994-1995 (Box-folder 373: 3)
    - 1997 (Box-folder 373: 4)
  - The Rape of Nanking: The Forgotten Holocaust of World War II book promotion, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 373: 5)
  - The Rape of Nanking: The Forgotten Holocaust of World War II film project, 1998-2003
    - 1998-1999 (Box-folder 373: 6)
    - 2000 (Box-folder 373: 7-8)
    - 2001 (Box-folder 373: 9-11)
    - 2001 (Box-folder 374: 1-3)
    - 2002 (Box-folder 374: 4)
    - 2003 (Box-folder 374: 5-10)
  - Renaissance Weekend, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 375: 1-3)
  - Speaking engagements, 1996-2004
    - 1996 (Box-folder 375: 4)
    - 1997 (Box-folder 375: 5)
    - 1998 (Box-folder 375: 6)
    - 1999 (Box-folder 375: 7)
    - 2000 (Box-folder 375: 8)
    - 2002 (Box-folder 375: 9)
    - 2003 (Box-folder 375: 10-11)
    - 2003 (Box-folder 376: 1-2)
    - 2004 (Box-folder 376: 3)
  - Thread of the Silkworm film project, 1998 (Box-folder 376: 4)
  - Wu, Carolyn, 1992 (Box-folder 376: 5)
- Speeches and writings by Iris Chang, 1993-1998
  - Interview conducted by Kinue Tokudome, 1998 October (Box-folder 376: 6)
  - Notes on ideas for books and screenplays, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 376: 7)
  - Speeches, 1993-1998
    - Speech on Tsien Hsue-shen, California Institute of Technology, Pasadena, California, 1993 April 8 (Box-folder 376: 8)
    - Speech on Nanking Massacre, Harvard Law School, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1997 (Box-folder 376: 9)
    - Speech on writing and publishing, Johns Hopkins University, Baltimore, Maryland, 1997 November 18 (Box-folder 376: 10)
    - Speech on writing, Santa Barbara Writers' Conference, Santa Barbara, California, 1998 (Box-folder 376: 11)
    - Speech on writing and publishing, Virginia Beach, Virginia, 1998 (Box-folder 376: 12)
    - Speech on Nanking Massacre, Commonwealth Club, San Francisco, California, 1998 February 19 (Box-folder 376: 13)
    - Speech on Nanking Massacre, United States Holocaust Museum, Washington, D.C., 1998 March 15 (Box-folder 376: 14)
    - Mock tribunal testimony, 1998 October 24 (Box-folder 376: 15)
    - Human Rights Night speech, San Francisco, California, 1998 December 9 (Box-folder 376: 16)
- Closed (Boxes 377-379)
- Brett Douglas correspondence file, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 380: 1)
- Clippings relating to Iris Chang, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 380: 2)
- Mailing list, 2003 (Box-folder 380: 4)
- Notes, 2003 (Box-folder 380: 5)
- Photographs depicting Iris Chang, 1999-2004 (Box-folder 380: 6)
- Travel itinerary and related correspondence, 2004 (Box-folder 380: 7)
- Correspondence, 1997-2004
  - General, 1997-2004
    - 1997-1999 (Box-folder 380: 8)
    - 2000-2001 (Box-folder 380: 9)
    - 2002 (Box-folder 380: 10)
    - 2003 (Box-folder 380: 11-12)
    - 2004 (Box-folder 380: 13-14)
  - Chang, Ying-Ying, 2001 (Box-folder 381: 1)
  - Mow, Van, 2004 (Box-folder 381: 2)
  - New Dimensions Broadcasting Network, 2003 (Box-folder 381: 3)
- Subject file, 1998-2004
  - Central Intelligence Agency, 2004 (Box-folder 381: 4)
  - Devil Pup program, 2004 (Box-folder 381: 5)
  - Everitt, Anthony, 2002 (Box-folder 381: 6)
  - Film projects, 2004 (Box-folder 381: 7)
  - Fulfillment services, 2004 (Box-folder 381: 8)
  - Furniture, 2002 (Box-folder 381: 9)
  - Media contacts, 1998-2003 (Box-folder 381: 10)
  - Near-death experiences, 2004 (Box-folder 381: 12-13)
  - Writing course (Box-folder 381: 14)
- Closed (Boxes 382-383)
- The Rape of Nanking: The Forgotten Holocaust of World War II film project file, 1998-2003
  - Articles, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 384: 1)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2003
    - General, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 384: 2)
    - Glasser, Barry, 2001 (Box-folder 384: 3)
    - Hepler, Chris and Jennifer Brandes, 2003 (Box-folder 384: 4)
    - Ho, Yim, 2001 (Box-folder 384: 5)
    - Kan, Jennifer, 2003 (Box-folder 384: 6)
    - Raina, Ranjit, 2001 (Box-folder 384: 7)
    - Rosen, Phillip, 2003 (Box-folder 384: 8)
    - Silberman, Gil, 2003 (Box-folder 384: 9)
    - Smiley, Shari, 2001 (Box-folder 384: 10)
    - Tugend, Jennie Lew, 2003 (Box-folder 384: 11)
    - Waterman, Stephen, 2000 (Box-folder 384: 12)
    - Wise, Christina, 2003 (Box-folder 384: 13)
  - Outlines and proposals, 2003 (Box-folder 384: 14)
  - Transcript of screenwriting course given by John Truby, 2001 (Box-folder 385: 1-4)
- Printed matter, 1965-2004
  - Comic books, 1965-1984
    - 1965-1970 (Box-folder 385: 5)
    - 1974-1977 (Box-folder 385: 6)
    - 1979-1984 (Box-folder 385: 7)
  - Program, 1999 (Box-folder 385: 8)
  - Serial issues, 1998-2004
    - 1998-2000 (Box-folder 385: 9)
    - 2002-2004 (Box-folder 385: 10)
- Closed (Boxes 386-394)
- Addresses, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 395: 1)
- Business cards, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 395: 2-8)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1998-2003
- Printed matter, 1997-2004
  - Clippings, 1999-2004 (Box-folder 396: 1)
  - Newsletters, 1997-2004 (Box-folder 396: 2)
  - Monographs by James J. Schmalstig, 2004 (Box-folder 396: 3-5)
- Closed (Boxes 397-412)